Adrià Mitjavila Ventura

Bioinformatician

☆ Girona (Spain) - Milan (Italy) adria.mitjavila94@gmail.com
amitjavilaventura.github.io amitjavilaventura amitjavilaventura

Biotechnologist living around computers, pursuing a PhD in Computational Biology and interested in data analysis to support experimental research as well as in pure computational experiments and in software/pipeline development.

Education	
PhD. Computational Biology, Scuola Europea di Medicina Molecolare, Milan (Italy)	2019 - Present
MSc. Bioinformatics and Biostatistics, Universitat Oberta de Catalunya, Online	2018 - Present
MSc. Molecular Genetics and Biotechnology, Universidad de Sevilla, Seville (Spain)	2017 - 2018
BSc. Biotechnology, Universitat de Girona, Girona (Spain)	2012 - 2017
Employment	
Istituto Europeo di Oncologia	Milan (Italy)
PhD Candidate in Computational Biology	10/2019 - Present
Bioinformatician	07/2019 - 10/2019
Instituto de Biomedicina de Sevilla	Seville (Spain)
Research assistant	07/2018 - 10/2018
Master's thesis student	09/2017 - 07/2018
Institut d'Investigació Biomèdica de Girona	Girona (Spain)
Research internship student	07/2017 - 09/2017
Microbial. Sistemes i aplicacions analítiques, S.L.	Girona (Spain)
Bachelor's thesis student	01/2017 - 06/2017
Internship student	09/2016 - 06/2017
n 111 d	

Publications _

JOURNAL ARTICLES

Begley et~al.~2020 Xrn1 influence on gene transcription results from the combination of general effects on elongating RNA pol II and gene-specific chromatin configuration. RNA~Biology.~DOI:~10.1080/15476286.2020.1845504.

References _

Available upon request.

Updated: Mar. 23, 2021 1/1